Finding Aid for Elly Peterson papers 1943-2006
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Scrapbooks/Clippings 1943-circa 1980
  The Scrapbooks/Clippings series (2 lin.ft.; 1943-ca. 1980), bound volumes and loose pages, includes material from her service with the Red Cross during World War II, documentation of her political acclivities with the Republican Party and ERAmerica. The scrapbooks contain clippings, some correspondence, event programs, and other memorabilia.
  - 1943-1945 American Red Cross, WWII, 2 folders (Box 22)
  - 1943-1945 American Red Cross, Miscellaneous (Box 22)
  - 1943-1945 American Red Cross, WWII, Loose Items, 2 folders (Box 22)
  - 1943-1945 American Red Cross, WWII (Box 22)
    bound and typed excerpts of correspondence from scrapbooks
  - 1960-1961 (Box 22)
    (unbound, incomplete)
  - 1963 (Volume 2)
  - 1964 (Volume 3)
  - 1964-1968 (Volume 4)
  - 1964 Senate Campaign (Box 22)
  - 1968 May, Surprise Birthday Party (Box 22)
  - 1969-1970 (Box 22)
    unbound, incomplete
  - April-December 1969 (Box 22)
  - 1970
    - January-March (Box 23)
    - April-June (Box 23)
    - July-December (Box 23)
  - Clippings (loose)
    - Senatorial Campaign 1964 (Box 23)
    - ERAmerica and Other Women's Rights Involvement 1964, 1969-1979 (Box 23)
    - General and Summary Articles on EMP and her Career 1962-1978 (Box 23)
    - Miscellaneous 1946-1977 (Box 23)
    - President Ford Committee 1976 (Box 23)
    - Republican Party Activities
      - 1961-64 (Box 23)
      - 1965-70 (Box 23)
    - Retirement from Republican National Convention 1970 (Box 23)
  - Scrapbook/photo albums
    - Trip to Russia 1969 (Box 24)
    - Trip to the Middle East 1974, 2 volumes (Box 24)
    - Trip to China October 1975 (Box 24)
Selective Index to Correspondents
Bliss, Ray Charles, 1907-1981.
Nov. 5, 1965, Jan. 17, 1966, Apr. 13, 1966, May 24, 1966, July 25, 1966, Oct. 17, 1966, Nov. 3, 1966, 1968
Bolger, Ray.
Apr. 15, 1968
Brooke, Edward William, 1919-
May 3, 1965
Chafee, John H., 1922-
Sept. 13, 1965
Dirksen, Everett McKinley.
Dec. 27, 1965
Evans, Daniel J., 1925-
Oct. 27, 1967
Ford, Gerald R., 1913-2006.
June 10, 1965
Hart, Philip A. (Philip Aloysius), 1912-1976.
Apr. 16, 1964, Sept. 9, 1964
Morton, Thruston B. (Thruston Ballard), 1907-1982.
Sept. 15, 1964, Mar. 15, 1965, Oct. 28, 1965
Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913-1994.
Dec. 6, 1965, Jan. 13, 1969
Percy, Charles H., 1919-
Apr. 17, 1967, Apr. 8, 1968
Riegle, Donald W., 1938-
Mar. 10, 1967
Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich), 1908-1979.
Apr. 9, 1964, Apr. 30, 1968
Romney, George W., 1907-1995.
Apr. 12, 1968
Stassen, Harold Edward, 1907-2001.
Feb. 22, 1966, Jan. 18, 1967
Wilson, Robert Carlton, 1909-
July 5, 1968